Register of the Mark Sullivan Papers, 1883-1952
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1883-1952
  - Johnston, Clifford C., 1930
  - Johnston, Mercer G., 1945
  - Johnston, Percey H., 1933
  - Jones, Ben, 1933
  - Jones, I.T., 1929
  - Jones, Miles W., 1939
  - Jones, Robert F., 1943
  - Jordan, D. E., 1925
  - Jordan, David Starr, 1924
  - Jordan, Virgil, 1933
  - Jung, Harry A., 1939 (Box 11.)
  - Jurtz, Muriel, 1938
  - Kable, George W., 1941
  - Kaiser, Emanuel M., 1935
  - Kansas State Teachers Association, 1935
  - Kaplan, Hillel, 1938
  - Keen, William W., 1927
  - Keep, T. S., n.d.
  - Keirn, Heber, 1935
  - Kellerman, R. S., 1945
  - Kelley, Mary McClure, 1934
  - Kellogg, Charles W., 1930
  - Kellogg, Fanny, 1945
  - Kellogg, Frank B., 1932-35
  - Kellogg, R. A., 1934
  - Kellogg, Vernon, 1925
  - Kelly, John Eoghan, 1935
  - Kelsey, Preston T., 1935
  - Kenyon, William S., 1932
  - Keppel, David, 1935
  - Kerbs, Richard H., 1941
  - Kerney, Jinn, 1932
  - Kester, W. T., 1917
  - Keyes, Homer E., 1938
  - Kieser, Paul W., 1935
  - Kilby, Glenn M., 1933
  - Killick, John A., 1932
  - Kincaid, Mary G., 1941
  - King, David W., 1920
  - King, Ernest J., 1943
  - King, Wilford I., 1946
  - Kinsey, F. S., 1932-33
  - Kirchhofer, A. M., 1933
  - Kirchway, George W., 1935
  - Klein, Katherine Thayer, 1939
  - Klinger, Harry S., n.d.
  - Klivans, Isadore, 1932
  - Knerr, Horace C., 1943
  - Knight, Jesse H., n.d.
  - Knowles, Horace G., 1927-30
  - Knox, Dodley W., 1929
  - Knox, Frank, 1920-29
  - Knox, Samuel L. G., 1939
  - Krupp, J. A., 1935
  - Kochendorfer, Chas. A., 1927
  - Kohlsaat, Herman H., 1922
  - Korner, Jules G., Jr., 1932
  - Kracht, Ernest D., 1940
  - Krueger, A. H., 1941
  - Kuehn, M. R., 1936
  - Kurzman, Charles, 1932
  - Lacey, E. P., 1929
  - Lafferty, John M., 1932
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello, 1938
  - Lahm, Frank P., 1927
  - Lakey, Alice, 1933
  - Lambright, Edwin D., 1928
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1921-35
  - LaMoore, Parker, 1930
  - LaMothe, Gertrude, 1934-35
  - Lanchashire, Sarah H., 1936
  - Lane, Gertrude B., 1934
  - Lane, Layle, 1942
  - Lane, Rose Wilder, 1938
  - Lange, Fred G., 1935
  - Lankford, William C., 1929
  - Larkin, John Adrian, 1933
  - Laron, Irving H., 1932
  - Lasker, Albert D., 1923-36
  - Law, John A., 1945
  - Lawrence, H. G., 1934
  - Lawson, William V., 1934
  - Leach, H. E., 1926
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1929
  - LeBoutillier, P., 1929
  - Leckie, A. S., 1920
  - Lee, Albert, 1931
  - Lee, P. Blair, 1934-45
  - Lefeber, Edward A., 1933
  - Lehlbach, Frederick R., 1920
  - Lehman, Maxwell, 1932
  - Leigh, W. Colston, 1935-36
  - Lissner, Meyer, 1920
  - Leiter, O. C., 1929
  - Leland, Dean R., 1935
  - Leland, Waldo G., 1928
  - LeMart, Eugenia, 1940-41
  - Lennon, Howard A., 1932-33
  - Lenroot, Irvine L., 1927, 1935
  - Leon, Rene, 1935
  - Leroy, Herbert, 1932
  - Levschner, E. P., 1893
  - Lewis, Jerome Hamilton, 1930
  - Lewis, William Draper, 1932
  - Lilber, George Jr., 1932
  - Lincoln, Edmond E., 1934-42
  - Lindsay, Samuel McCerie, 1920
  - Lindsey, Ben B., 1910-14
  - Lingham, Fred J., 1936-42
  - Linhoss, E. F., 1932
  - Linn, Henry A., 1933
  - Linton, Morris A., 1935
  - Lippman, Walter, 1931
  - Lisman, Frederick J., 1933-34 (Box 12.)
  - Lissner, Meyer, 1920
  - Litchfield, Dorthy Hale, 1926
  - Little, J. E., 1931-32
  - Little, Walter H., 1931
  - Livengood, William S., 1941
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1923
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr., 1935
  - Loeb, William 1932
  - Loeb, William Jr., n.d.
  - Logan, Donald F., 1935-36
  - Lohmann, Carl L., 1929
  - Lombard, Norman, 1929-31
  - Long, W. M., 1932
  - Longworth, Alice, 1935
  - Loree, Leonar, F., 1933
  - Lorimer, George H., 1934-35
  - Lough, William H., 1914
  - Lovejoy, Phillip C., 1934
  - Loun, Elizabeth, 1941
  - Lowry, C. W., 1932
  - Lucas, Robert H., 1935
  - Lucas, Scott W., 1939
  - Luce, Clair Boothe, 1938-44
  - Ludlow, Louis, 1930
  - Lull, Robert W., 1930
  - Lyon, Charles W., 1931
  - Lyons, Maurice F., 1920
  - Lysons, J. W., 1932
  - McAdams, William D., 1941
  - McAdoo, Malcolm R., 1924-28
  - McAdoo, William G., 1921-35
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1935
  - MacArthur, William C., 1944
  - McBride, John A., 1931-32
  - McCahill, Charles F., 1934
  - McCamant, Wallace, 1935
  - McCoy, H.H., 1908
  - McClelland, W. E., 1932
  - McClintock, R. M., 1931
  - McCorkle, G. K., 1935
  - McCormick, Joseph Medill, 1923
  - McCormick, Robert R., 1932
  - McCormick, Ruth, 1925-30
  - McCormick, Vance C., 1923
  - McCulloh, J. S., 1934-41
  - McCurdy, Allen, 1920
  - McDiarmind, Henry W., 1927
  - MacDonald, Kenneth, n.d.
  - Macdonnel, J. S., 1937
  - MacDowell, Lloyd W., 1918
  - MacDuffee, T. C., 1935
  - MacEntee, William, 1937
  - Macfarlane, Peter C., 1921
  - MacGraw, J. J., 1923
  - McGregor, Alexander G., 1931
  - McHugh, H. Bart, 1934
  - MacHugh, Mabel B., 1936
  - McIntosh, James H., 1906
  - McIntosh, James W., 1927
  - Mack, Connie, 1936
  - MacKaye, James, 1906-1907
  - McKee, Homer, 1918
  - McKelvie, Samuel R., 1922-33
  - McKenney, H. J., 1932
  - McKenzie, W. F., 1924
  - Mackway, Harold, 1935
  - McLaughlin, Hannag, 1938
  - McLean, Angus W., 1927
  - MacLenathan, Paul, 1923
  - MacLeod, William P., 1921
  - McManis, Terence J., 1934
  - McMorrow, Thomas, 1929
  - McNab, Gavin, 1920
  - McNary, Charles L., 1924-35
  - Macy, W. Kingsland, 1926
  - Madsen, H. T., 1935
  - Madison, Maury, 1932
  - Magie, Carlton C., 1935
  - Magee, H. J., 1935-37
  - Magee, James D., 1920
  - Mahony, Walter B., 1935
  - Main, Mrs. David, 1933
  - Mallon, Winfred, 1938
  - Malone, Dudley Field, 1915
  - Maquarie, Arthur, 1918
  - Marcosson, Isaac, 1917 (Box 13.)
  - Marcy, Fred, 1932
  - Margetts, Walter T., 1943-44
  - Maris, H. B., 1943
  - Markham, Edgar, 1931
  - Marshall, John, 1945
  - Marshall, W. H., 1925
  - Martin, Attwood R., 1944
  - Martin, Douglas V. Jr., 1937
  - Martin, Earle, 1934
  - Martin, Edward, 1933
  - Marvin, Langdon P., 1934-35
  - Marx, Groucho, 1932
  - Masland, F. E., 1923
  - Mason, Mrs. Frank S., 1941
  - Mason, Julian S., 1935
  - Matheson, Alfred L., 1941
  - Mathews, Jerry A., 1937
  - Maverick, Maury, 1937-42
  - Mayer, F. von Rossdell, 1934
  - Meade, Charles A., 1926
  - Mebane, Daniel, 1943
  - Mecham, Al, 1935
  - Meckstroth, Jacob A., 1935
  - Melcher, Henry K., 1932
  - Mellar, Elizabeth B., n.d.
  - Melvin, Ridgely P., 1920
  - Merritt, Carroll B., 1924
  - Merritt, Walter Gordon, 1931-37
  - Metcalf, Jesse H., 1927
  - Meyer, Eugene Jr., 1921-34
  - Michelson, Charles 1935
  - Middleton, W. E., 1920
  - Migel, J.A., 1945
  - Miles, E. Scott, 1932-34
  - Miller, Adolph Casper, 1935
  - Miller, Arthur Lewis, 1944
  - Miller, Clyde R., 1937
  - Miller, James S., 1944
  - Miller, John D., 1941
  - Miller, John H., 1896
  - Miller, THomas W., 1935
  - Miller, W. H., 1935-38
  - Miller, William J., 1940
  - Milliman, T. E., 1942
  - Mills, Borden H., 1944
  - Mills, Mrs. John Kane, 1932
  - Mills, Ogden L., 1920-35
  - Milner, Harry R., 1930-32
  - Milton, George Fort, 1927-43
  - Miner, Edward G., 1930-34
  - Minnich, Harvey C., 1932
  - Mish, Frank W., 1920
  - Mitchell, Edwin Knox, 1929
  - Mitchell, William D., 1935-44
  - Mitke, Charles A., 1934
  - Miura, T., 1934
  - Moir, Phyllis, 1935
  - Montague, Gilbert H., 1928-34
  - Moody, Dan, 1928
  - Moore, Alexander P., 1923
  - Moore, F. H., 1920
  - Moore, John Bassett, 1932
  - Moore, Joseph Hampton, 1932-35
  - Moore, Otis, 1930
  - Moore, Robert Walton, 1923-29
  - Moore, Roy D., 1935
  - Moreton, Ralph E., 1945
  - Morey, Gladys E., 1942
  - Morgan, Anne, 1943
  - Morgan, E. D., 1933
  - Morgan, G. C., 1935
  - Morgan, J. R., 1924
  - Morison, George A., 1938
  - Morris, Ann, 1938
  - Morris, C. G., 1933
  - Morris, J. D., 1932-36
  - Morriss, F. E., 1945
  - Morse, Jamin Seth, 1930
  - Morse, Stanley F., 1934-46
  - Morton, James A., 1931
  - Moses, George H., 1935
  - Mott, Frank L., 1935 (Box 14.)
  - Mott, John R., 1933
  - Motter, Harve H., 1920
  - Moulton, F. R., 1945
  - Mount, Wadsworth W., 1935-43
  - Moyer, Thomas J., 1931
  - Mudd, Sydney E., 1920
  - Mudd, W. S., 1934
  - Mulcahy, J. B., 1920
  - Mullen, John P., 1943
  - Mulligan, John A., 1935
  - Mullins, George W., 1933
  - Mulvane, David W., 1920
  - Mummert, Sterling P., 1945
  - Mumper, Norris, 1942
  - Mundt, Karl, 1941
  - Munroe, Mrs. Kirk, 1933-36
  - Murchie, Robert C., 1920
  - Murdock, Victor, 1931
  - Murphy, Donald R., 1927
  - Murphy, Mary C., 1941
  - Murphy, William C., 1934
  - Murray, Elsie, 1945
  - Murray, Robert H., 1939
  - Myers, William Starr, 1935-39
  - Myrick, N. Sumner, 1930
  - Nagle, A. F., 1935
  - Nash, Bradley, 1933
  - Nast, Conde, 1931
  - National Foreign Trade Council, Inc., 1940
  - Naylor, Stanley, 1918
  - Neal, O. E., 1934-35
  - Needham, Henry Beech, 1906-09
  - Nelson, John H., 1941
  - Nelson, Theodore J., 1934
  - Nevstadt, Herbert, 1942
  - Nevins, W. H., 1935
  - New, Harry S., 1935
  - Newberry, Truman H., 1935
  - Newcomb, Harry T., 1934
  - Newman, Maud B., 1932-33
  - Newmeyer, A. G., 1920
  - Newton, Walter H., 1935-36
  - Neylan, John F., 1920
  - Neymann, A., 1934
  - Nicoll, Constance, 1932
  - Nieman, Lucas W., 1919
  - Nimmo, H. M., 1932
  - Noble, N. J., 1926
  - Norman, Norman C., 1935-41
  - Northcliffe, Alfred C.W.H., 1914-17
  - Northwood, Arthur Jr., 1935
  - Norton, D. N., 1936
  - Norton, George W., 1922
  - Nowland, Otho, 1941
  - Oberle, W. J., 1944
  - O'Brien, Robert L., 1923-35
  - Odell, Benjamin B., 1925
  - O'Donnell, Charles L., 1930
  - Offutt, Mrs. Charles, 1935
  - Ogg, W. R., 1942
  - Older, Fremont, 1919
  - Olessan, Anna D., 1922
  - Olson, Kenneth E., 1935
  - Orvic, A. D., 1936
  - Osborn, Chase S., 1932
  - O'Shaughnessy, Edith C., n.d.
  - Otis, Elizabeth F., n.d.
  - Ousley, Clarence, 1927
  - Owen, O., 1910
  - Owens, John W., 1933
  - Packard, Robert Lee, n.d.
  - Page, Arthur W., 1923-28
  - Page, Walter H., 1914
  - Paine, Albert Bigelow, 1929
  - Palmer, Charles M., 1904
  - Palmer, Frederick Jr., 1935
  - Palmer, Frederick R., n.d.
  - Parker, Chauncey G., 1934
  - Parker, Jameson, 1934-38
  - Parker, Helen F., 1945
  - Parker, John M., 1920
  - Parker, Walter, 1929
  - Parker, William B., 1933
  - Parker, J. L., 1927
  - Parmer, Charles B., 1921
  - Parsons, Frances, 1926
  - Persons, Herbert, 1920
  - Persons, James O., 1935
  - Parton, Hugo, 1912
  - Pattangell, Mrs. G. M., 1922
  - Patten, Thomas G., 1922
  - Patterson, Ernest Minor, 1934
  - Patterson, Henry Carter, 1938-40
  - Patterson, Isabel, n.d.
  - Paxson, Frederic L., 1935
  - Payne, George Henry, 1923 (Box 15.)
  - Payne, John Barton, 1923
  - Peacock, Roscoe, 1936-45
  - Peason, Edmund L., n.d.
  - Pearson, Frank A., 1932-33
  - Pearson, Paul M., 1922
  - Peek, George N., 1942
  - Peirce, Mary B., 1935-36
  - Perkins, Frances, 1938
  - Perkins, Fred, 1934-46
  - Peters, John A., 1920
  - Peterson, Elmer T., 1935
  - Petit, William M., 1935
  - Petree, W. A., 1941
  - Phelph, Charles S., 1936
  - Philips, Jesse E., 1904
  - Phillips, George M., 1918
  - Phillips, R. S., 1920
  - Phipps, Lawrence C., 1935
  - Pickering, Chas. I., 1935
  - Pierson, Lewis E., 1933
  - Pinchot, Cornelia Bryce, 1924
  - Pinet, F. L., 1935
  - Piquet, John A., 1922
  - Placer, S. Frederick, 1934
  - Platt, Edmund, 1930-33
  - Pleissener, Karl R., 1920
  - Poindexter, Miles, 1911-18
  - Polnig, Daniel A., 1935
  - Pomerance, Atlee, 1935
  - Poor, Horace F., 1921
  - Pope, Hope Cox, 1926
  - Porterfield, Allen W., 1927
  - Potter, Arthur G., 1934
  - Potter, M. S., n.d.
  - Potter, William B., 1917
  - Potter, William C., 1933
  - Pound, Arthur, 1926
  - Powell, Harford, 1919-21
  - Powers, David E., 1928
  - Pratt, Ruth Sears Baker, 1930
  - Prendergast, William A., 1932
  - Price, Arthur L., 1945
  - Prince, Theodore, 1932
  - Printing Equipment Industry and Trade, 1934
  - Pritchard, S. F., 1921
  - Pritchett, Henry S., 1931
  - Procope, Hjalmar J.F., 1941
  - Proctor, William, 1935
  - Putnam, Nina Wilcox, 1940
  - Pyle, Robert, 1941
  - Radcliffe, Amos H., 1920
  - Radford, Stephen, 1941
  - Rahn, A.A.D., 1932
  - Rainey, Henry T., 1920
  - Ramsayer, Christian W., 1931
  - Ramsey, Edward P., 1934
  - Randolph, Jennings, 1937
  - Randenbush, G. B., 1941
  - Rawson, Charles A., 1920
  - Rea, John H., 1929
  - Record, George L., 1920
  - Redding, Henry W., 1945
  - Redfield, Emanuel, 1934
  - Reed, Charles A., 1930
  - Reed, David A., 1935
  - Reed, James A., 1918
  - Reeves, Harrison, 1940-41
  - Reeves, Samuel, 1934
  - Reid, Elizabeth M., 1922
  - Reid, Helen, 1941
  - Reiling, Howard A., 1934
  - Reiter, Hannah M., 1945
  - Rennuel, Arthur K., 1937
  - Reppy, Alison, 1937
  - Reynolds, James Bronson, 1907
  - Reynolds, James Burton, 1935
  - Rhoade, Charles J., 1937
  - Rhoades, J. Howard, 1942
  - Rice, Harry E., 1934-35
  - Richards, Bernard G., 1929
  - Richards, L. D., 1923
  - Richardson, John, 1942
  - Richey, Lawrence, 1932
  - Richter, Horace, 1939
  - Rickard, Edgar, 1929-36
  - Ricks, Walter, 1935
  - Riddell, George D., 1922
  - Rieves, Clifford B., 1938
  - Rinehart, J. B., 1905-06
  - Ritchie, Albert C., 1923-31
  - Robbins, Barney R., 1944
  - Roberts, Kenneth, 1933 (Box 16.)
  - Roberts, Owen, 1935
  - Robertson, Ben, 1939
  - Robinson, Claude E., 1929-30
  - Robinson, Corine Roosevelt, 1925-30
  - Robinson, E. Dunning, 1935
  - Robinson, George P., 1934
  - Robinson, Henry M., 1932-35
  - Robinson, John B., 1892
  - Robinson, M. Douglas, n.d.
  - Rochester, Junius C., 1935
  - Roche, Thomas F., 1929
  - Rodenburg, Lilyan H., 1937
  - Rodgers, W. B., 1921
  - Rogers, Cameron, 1929
  - Rogers, Elysa Howard, 1926
  - Rogers, Francis, 1919
  - Rogers, Julia C., 1941
  - Roosevelt, Edith [UNK], n.d.
  - Roosevelt, Philip J., 1912
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1908-10
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Jr., 1932-35
  - Root, Elihu, 1927
  - Rose, William G., 1934
  - Rosewater, Victor, 1932
  - Ross, Charles L., 1929
  - Ross, Galen Starr, 1941-45
  - Rote, Stuart Beaver, 1937
  - Roth, Minnie M., 1936
  - Rountree, H. F., 1929
  - Rowan, Andrew S., 1930
  - Rowe, Ellen, 1933
  - Rowe, Leo S., 1932
  - Rowell, Chester H., 1918-20
  - Royster, Vermont, 1951
  - Ruhl, Arthur, 1922
  - Rukeyser, Merryle, 1938
  - Rumely, Edward A., 1936
  - Runyan, W. Cleveland, 1935
  - Rupert, George Harris, 1930
  - Russell, Phillip H., 1936
  - Rutherford, Geddes W., 1923
  - Rutherford, George E., 1938
  - Ryan, Patricia, 1945
  - Saachy, Irene, 1938
  - Sager, E. E., 1937
  - Sames, Albert M., 1920
  - Samuels, Morris, 1937
  - Sanborn, Ladd Frisby, 1941
  - Sanford, Harold W., 1934
  - Sanford, Hugh W., 1937
  - Sargent, Noel, 1933
  - Sasse, A. H., 1935
  - Satterlee, Herbert L., 1935
  - Saunders, M. G., 1920
  - Saville, Frances E., 1941
  - Savitz, Jerohn J., 1936
  - Scallan, Robert O., 1935
  - Scaaf, Ruth, 1945
  - Schertz, Frank M., 1933
  - Schlaudecker, J. B., 1927
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M., 1935
  - Schley, Reeve, 1924
  - Schneider, Isidor, 1936
  - Schneider, William R., 1945
  - Schnitzler, John W., 1929
  - Schofield, Tom, 1933
  - Schultz, Wilbur E., 1934
  - Schweiger, W. F., 1935
  - Scott, Albert L., 1935
  - Scott, Herbert, 1943
  - Scott, Lee C., 1936
  - Scott, S. D., 1936
  - Scott, Walter Dill, 1936
  - Scranton, Marion M.W., 1934-35
  - Scribner, Arthur H., 1927
  - Seasongood, Murray, 1935-36
  - Sedgwick, Ellery, 1922-27
  - Seely, F. L., 1928
  - Seibert, Albert E., 1926
  - Seibold, Louis, 1935
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1932-33
  - Selvage, James P., 1941
  - Selvin, Edwin, 1918
  - Seymour, Helen, 1941
  - Sexton, Emory, 1943
  - Shallcross, W. C., 1943
  - Sharp, Gordon Doremus, 1940
  - Sharp, J. Clarence, 1942
  - Sharp Motor Company, 1934
  - Shattuck, Robert, 1945
  - Shaw, Arch W., 1942
  - Shea, William E., 1928
  - Sheba, S., 1922
  - Shedd, Charles Gale, 1920
  - Shelby, Oliver Hazard Perry, 1920
  - Shepherd, W. C., 1920
  - Sheriden, George V., 1920
  - Sherman, Lawrence Y., 1920
  - Sherman, Maurice Sinclair, 1931-34
  - Shern, Daniel J., 1945
  - Sherrill, Fred G., 1929
  - Shimer, William A., 1939
  - Shipley, W. S., 1934
  - Shirk, Stanley, 1926-30 (Box 17.)
  - Shoemaker, William D., 1932
  - Shortlidge, Raymond S., 1934
  - Shoudy, W. A., 1939
  - Shutts, Frank B., 1928
  - Silbert, Beverly, 1938
  - Simmons, Maurice, 1940
  - Simond, Frank, 1933
  - Simons, Robert G., 1934-35
  - Simpson, F. B., 1940
  - Singh, J. J., 1942
  - Singmaster, James A., 1935
  - Slemp, C. Bascom, n.d.
  - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr., 1939
  - Sloan, George A., 1935
  - Smith, A. W., 1936-37
  - Smith, Allan K., 1934
  - Smith, Charles D., 1939
  - Smith, D. D., 1927
  - Smith, Edgar F., 1934
  - Smith, Edward E., 1920-30
  - Smith, Ethel, 1930
  - Smith, Frederic L., 1932
  - Smith, Gerald L. K., 1941
  - Smith, Gertrude, 1930
  - Smith, H. S., 1937
  - Smith, Henry C., 1938-45
  - Smith, Howard W., 1944
  - Smith, Joseph D., 1934
  - Smith, J. Henderson, 1934
  - Smith, Marion B., 1945
  - Smith, W. Everett, 1929
  - Snook, A. M., 1920
  - Snow, George A., 1934
  - Snow, John B., 1935
  - Snyder, Carl, 1930-32
  - Snyder, H. Rossitor, 1945
  - Sokolsky, George, 1937
  - Sollitt, Ralph, 1935
  - Somerville, H. P., 1934
  - Soper, Morris, 1932-52
  - Spahr, Walter E., 1939
  - Sparkes, Boyden, 1935
  - Spear, John A., 1944
  - Speers, James M., 1937
  - Spencer, John C., 1919
  - Sperry, Edward G., 1936
  - Speyer, James, 1935
  - Spiess, Mathias, 1935
  - Spoehrer, Jane B., 1935
  - Sprague, Roger, 1930
  - Sproul, William C., 1922
  - Squires, Duane, 1935
  - Stableford, Isa, 1938
  - Stackpole, Edward J., 1929-30
  - Starr, Clarence T., 1925
  - Starrett, Paul, 1937
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1943-47
  - Stearns, Frank W., 1935
  - Stedman, Alfred D., 1935-41
  - Steed, Wickham, 1914-23
  - Stettinuis, Edward R. Jr., 1938
  - Stevens, D. Stockton, 1945
  - Stevenson, Archibald, 1935-44
  - Stewart, John L., 1928-36
  - Stewart, Robert Murray, 1936
  - Stewart, Robert W., 1935
  - Stickel, Fred G. Jr., 1942
  - Stillwell, Chas. J., 1935
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1932
  - Stimson, Marshall, 1910-29
  - Stockton, Gilchrist B., 1928-45
  - Stockton, Herbert K., 1937
  - Stoddard, Henry L., 1930-32
  - Stokes, Harold P., 1923-35
  - Stoltz, Mrs. James L., 1934
  - Stone, Elizabeth H., 1938
  - Stone, Harlan F., 1925
  - Stone, John Timothy, 1935
  - Storms, G. E., 1941
  - Story, C. H., 1909
  - Story, John P. Jr., 1936
  - Stott, Frederic, W. H., 1932 (Box 18.)
  - Stout, Tom, 1920
  - Stout, Weseley W., 1934
  - Stowe, Beecher, 1929
  - Straight, Willard D., 1913
  - Strang, Peter M., 1934
  - Strauss, Lewis, 1942
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1933
  - [UNK], Oscar S., 1923
  - Strauss, Robert K., 1935
  - Street, J. Glenn, 1936
  - Streit, Clarence K., 1940
  - Streit, Julian, 1914-39
  - Stringer, Kathleen Snow, 1935
  - Stringfellow, George E., 1930-34
  - Strongheart, A. J., 1942
  - Strother, French, 1922-29
  - Strous, Guy C., 1936
  - Styer, David, 1945
  - Sullivan family, 1883-1945
  - Sullivan, Clyde, 1920
  - Sullivan, John T., 1925-26
  - Sullivan, Lawrence, 1934-41
  - Sumnerill, William, 1920
  - Surface, Frank, 1927
  - Suydam, Henry, 1935
  - Swanson, Claude A., 1909
  - Swope, Gerard, 1935
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1932-43
  - Taft, Harry Lee, 1937
  - Talbot, E. C., 1935
  - Talbott, Ardue Lee, 1927
  - Talbott, Chas. G., 1935
  - Tanner, Frederick C., 1932
  - Taylor, C. W., 1933
  - Taylor, E. H., 1937
  - Taylor, Edward Thomas, 1920
  - Taylor, Henry Copeland, 1943
  - Taylor, Marshall, 1929
  - Taylor, Mason E., 1934
  - Taylor, P. R., 1934
  - Taylor, R. A., 1944
  - Tearman, J. F., 1926
  - Thayer, Aaron C., 1930
  - Thomas, Gus, 1922
  - Thomas, Harry N., 1927
  - Thompson, Charles Willis, 1935
  - Thompson, Edward A., 1945
  - Thompson, Frederic I., n.d.
  - Thompson, Huston, 1922
  - Thompson, Milton T., n.d.
  - Thompson, Ruth Plumly, 1936
  - Thompson, William Boyce, 1920
  - Thomson, James M., 1920-42
  - Thornburg, Don, 1935
  - Tieton, E., n.d.
  - Tillett, Mrs. S. B., 1945
  - Timberlake, Charles B., 1920
  - Tinsdale, G. M., 1934
  - Titus, W. W., 1920
  - Todd, Jane H., 1935
  - Tomilson, N.B., 1920
  - Tompkins, Edwin W., 1943
  - Tonor, Edward C., 1919
  - Towle, Herbert L., 1941
  - Towne, Charles A., 1928
  - Townsend, R. D., 1904
  - Train, Arthur, 1935
  - Trainer, John Newlin, 1931
  - Treadwell, George L., 1935
  - Treanor, A. R., 1920
  - Trenton Times, 1920
  - Triar, S., 1934
  - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1920-38
  - Turner, Arnold J., 1941
  - Underwood, J. Arthur, 1933
  - Underwood, W. G., 1930
  - Ungerer, Heiby W., 1935
  - Vandeburg, C. M., 1941
  - Vandegrift, W. A., 1929-30
  - Vandenberg, Arthur, 1939-42
  - Vanden Bosch, J. W., 1934
  - Vanderlip, Frank Arthur, 1918-35
  - Van Der Veer, Mrs. Francis S., 1941
  - Van Doren, Irita, 1951-52
  - Van Hoesen, Mrs. Frank P., 1941
  - Vary, Calvin P.H., 1935 (Box 19.)
  - Verdier, William E., 1935
  - Vernon, Paul E., 1935
  - Vernor, Henry E., 1928
  - Vizzard, William, 1909
  - Vogelsang, Alexander T., 1920
  - VonKummer, G. F., 1927
  - Wadham, Charles K., 1926
  - Wadsworth, Eliot, 1928
  - Wadsworth, James W., 1934-35
  - Wagner, Ruth, 1945
  - Wainwright, Jonathan M., 1932-34
  - Waldman, Henry, 1943
  - Walker, Roberts, 1911
  - Wallace, Anna M., 1941
  - Wallace, Dewitt, 1938
  - Wallace, Henry, 1937
  - Walsh, John, 1935
  - Walsh, Paul, 1935
  - Walsh, Thomas J., 1920-28
  - Walsh, Ulysses, 1932
  - Waltman, Franklin Jr., 1936
  - Walton, A. B., 1927-29
  - Waples, Rufus, 1937
  - Warburg, James P., 1936
  - Warren, Charles, 1924-41
  - Warren, Charles B., 1935
  - Warren, Francis E., 1923
  - Warrick, Don E., 1936
  - Washburn, Harold C., 1943
  - Washburn, Stanley, 1932
  - Wason, Edward H., 1920
  - Watkins, L.K., 1935
  - Watson, Max, 1923
  - Watts, Harvey M., n.d.
  - Way, Thomas A., 1926
  - Webb, E. H., 1945
  - Webb, Edgar, 1930
  - Webb, F. Egerton, 1932
  - Webb, M. C., 1935
  - Weber, Marjorie H., 1928
  - Weed, Merrill, 1935
  - Weinberg, Leonard, 1934
  - Welch, Orville, A., 1926
  - Welch, Roland A., 1934
  - Welliver, Judson C., 1935
  - Wells, Chester, 1943
  - Wells, Herbert G., 1921
  - Wells, John D., 1929
  - Wendkos, Philip, 1935
  - West, Lydia, 1929
  - West, Roy O., 1932
  - Westhoff, Gisela, 1927
  - Wheeler, Wayne B., 1926
  - Whataker, Spier, 1935
  - White, David M., n.d.
  - White, Doris O., 1945
  - White, Elizabeth H., 1936
  - White, Elsie Fellows, 1928-32
  - White, George, 1920
  - White, George, 1935
  - White, H. G., 1920
  - White, James C., 1925
  - White, Leroy G., 1934
  - White, Margaret Moffat, 1934
  - White, Walter, 1930
  - White, William Allen, 1924
  - Whitney, F. G., 1935
  - Whitney, Travis H., 1903-04
  - Whitney, V. G., 1930
  - Wickersham, George W., 1923
  - Wickes, Elbert A., 1935
  - Wiggin, Albert H., 1933
  - Wilber, Ray Lyman, 1924-44
  - Wilcox, Elizabeth G., 1935
  - Wilder, E. M., 1924
  - Wile, Fred W., n.d.
  - Wilkie, Wendell L., 1940
  - Wilkenson, Horace S., 1933
  - Willard, Paul, 1935
  - Willebrandt, Mabel Walker, 1935
  - Willert, Florence, n.d.
  - Williams, Aubrey W., 1935
  - Williams, Clay, 1935
  - Williams, H. W., 1934
  - Williams, John E., 1918
  - Williams, Nathan Boone, 1938
  - Williams, Paul B., 1924
  - Williams, Percy M., 1941
  - Williams, Walter, 1918
  - Williams, Walter W., 1924
  - Williams, Wayne C., 1932
  - Williams, Willian E., 1933
  - Wilson, C. Y., 1908
  - Wilson, C. M., 1942
  - Wilson, Vera B., 1935
  - Wilson, W. B., 1935
  - Winslow, Bertha Russell, 1922-27 (Box 20.)
  - Winton, Roy W., 1933-41
  - Wisewell, Francis H., 1936
  - Wister, Owen, 1922
  - Wood, W. E., 1930
  - Woodburg, Clarence, 1933
  - Woodlock, Thomas F., n.d.
  - Woods, William S., 1928
  - Woodward, R. L., 1925
  - Woodward, Roland B., 1934-35
  - Work, Herbert, 1923
  - Wright, Chester M., 1935
  - Wright, Hugh W., 1938
  - Wright, Joshua Butler, 1933